Robertson Lovell McClure

May 14th, 2016

(647) 229-4608

r.mcclure@mail.utoronto.ca http://robertsonmcclure.ca

I am a third year student-athlete at the University of Toronto pursuing a Major in Mathematics and a Specialist's Degree in Computer Science. When I'm not being paid to develop software, or paying to learn about developing software, you can find me reading books about software.

Skills

Python Java C HTML/CSS JavaScript SVN Git Vim

Employment

Software Developer

StockRender

Summer of 2016

• Develop an API for the terminal, a product StockRender sells to hedge funds.

Sports Analytics Developer

UofT Strength & Conditioning Summer of 2016

• Create a database to store Strength Data and automate the processing of daily survey results

Head Referee / Convener

UofT Intramural Volleyball

2015 - Present

• Hire, train and schedule volleyball officials for the 10+ matches that occur every weekday

Recruiting Assistant

UofT Mens Volleyball

2015 - Present

• Facilitate campus tours to potential recruits, communicate with all athletes who are interested in being recruited and assist recruits in navigating UofT's application process

Statistician

UofT Mens Volleyball

2014 - Present

2012 - Present

• Scout opponents using Data Project Software and report in-game statistics to coaching staff

Certified Volleyball Official

Ontario Volleyball Association

- Ensure that match play occurs in accordance to Volleyball Canada Rules
- Apply interpretation of rules to in-game scenarios

Mathematics Tutor

Self-Employed

2014 - 2015

- Teach first year calculus and linear algebra in a comprehensive manner
- Create individualized lesson plan for each student to cater to their needs

Counsellor

Camp Tawingo

2013 - 2015

- Responsible for 8 ten year old boys at over night camp for their three week stay
- Organize themed programs and games for campers

Volunteer Positions

Website Administrator & Videographer The Reading Line

2015 - Present

- Update TheReadingLine.ca and design the user experience as the web-traffic increases
- Create promotional videos, which includes directing, producing, filming and editing.

Sitting Volleyball Data Entry Volunteer Parapan American Games Summer of 2015

• Use volleyball terminology to translate the game into live statistics in a fast paced environment

Volleyball Data Entry Volunteer Pan American Games Summer of 2015

• Use volleyball terminology to translate the game into live statistics in a fast paced environment

Creative Director 100in1day | Slow Down Jane Summer of 2015

- Create promotional videos, which includes directing, producing, filming and editing.
- Advise on outreach plans to local communities

Elected Positions

Athlete and Team Manager

UofT Mens Volleyball

2014 - Present

- Commit over two hours every day to the team
- Responsible for the team's equipment including the camera, food supplements, etc.
- Prompt execution of miscellaneous jobs at the discretion of the Head Coach

Gate House President

Victoria College

2015 - Present

- Organize social events including a Pub Night and Traditional Ceremonies
- Represent the needs of Gate House at the Building Council Meetings

Math Union Treasurer

University of Toronto

2015 - Present

- Responsible for the allocation of funds and balancing the budget
- Reimburse Math Union members for approved purchases and manage the bank account

Math Union Social Officer

University of Toronto

2014 - 2015

- Organize catered social events in conjuncture with other unions
- Responsible for acquiring and transporting food to and from the venue

Athletic Representative

Gate House Council

2014 - 2015

- Advertise Varsity Athletics to Gate House
- · Assist in organizing athletic events for Gate House Members

Athletic Banquet Coordinator

UTS Athletics

2014

- Organize a 3 hour catered award event that featured multiple key note speakers
- Master of Ceremonies

Volleyball Coach

UTS Athletics

2011 - 2014

• Plan practices, coach volleyball and travel with the team to tournaments

Education

B.Sc. Math B.Sc. Computer Science Ontario Secondary School Diploma Awards	University of Toronto University of Toronto University of Toronto Schools	Class of 2019 Class of 2019 Class of 2014
Dean's Leadership Scholar Award	Faculty of Kinesiology	2016
Professor R. K. Arnold Scholarship Regents Admissions Scholarship Presidents Entrance Scholarship	Victoria University Victoria University University of Toronto	2015 2014 2014
University of Toronto Schools Diploma Ontario Scholar	University of Toronto Schools University of Toronto Schools	2014 2014